Where am I?
Oh, it's nice.
Hmm?
What's that?
Whoa!
What the...
Saotome.
Kuno!
You're my love.
RANMA1/2
BECAUSE THERE'S SOMEONE HE LIKES
Tendo, let's go today!
Saotome, step away from her now!
Ugh. Give me a break already.
I hate men!
Why is this here?
It's a present.
- No thanks.
- Hey!
Who said it was for you, Nabiki Tendo?
It's for the...
Uh, for the...
The adorable girl with the braid.
I wasted my soy milk because of you.
You narcissist.
A set of five for 3,000 yen.
This is my girl with the braid!
Oh, her guard's all the way down.
Kinda like a boy, right?
It's not very respectable.
You switched off Akane way too fast.
Who said I switched off?
You're not hoping to cheat on her?
That's not very nice.
Akane is pure and innocent.
And the pigtailed girl's a sporty beauty.
They're both so cute,
I simply can't let either of them go!
So my heart is crying out for the chance
to date the both of them simultaneously!
So in other words...
you're wanting to two-time this girl!
Set of five for 4,000.
You heartless entrepreneur.
- Deal!
- Cash, please.
Hey, Ranma.
Kuno wants to see you.
Really? What does he want now?
What is she up to?
Wh-What the hell are you doing?
That's what I want to know!
If you wish to give her a gift,
doing so through Ranma would be
the most expedited way.
- No thanks.
- Whoa, careful with that!
You should just forget
about that girl already.
What?
If I made a wild guess, I'd bet
you'll probably never see her again.
Wait. No, hold on.
What did you say?
You should accept that the two of you
live in different worlds.
Hey, man. What if someone was down there?
Never see her again?
What do you mean by that, Saotome?
He's quick
when he's running away.
Ouch! Uh-oh.
Hmph. My pigtailed girl!
I'm never letting go of you!
- Apologies in advance for this, Ranma.
- That's hot!
Ranma?
Get your hands off me.
Stop holding me, you idiot!
Do you finally get it now? See you.
Hold it!
I will not be fooled
by some cheap party tricks!
Huh? What? You don't get it.
Huh.
All right, listen carefully.
The girl with the braid...
Her body and soul...
...they all belong to Ranma!
Hmm?
You understand, don't you?
Huh?
- You are an enemy of women!
- Hey!
You're getting the wrong idea.
I will destroy you!
I'm using my power to save her!
Oh, really?
Okay then. If you lose this match,
you give up on the girl with the braid.
Never!
Huh?
- Whoa!
- Gotcha!
You can't get away.
Whoa!
Huh?
Hi, Akane.
Just for your information,
Kuno can get brutal against men.
All he needs to do is
get serious enough about it.
Ooh. And just for your information,
blue panties don't look good on you.
Go die for all I care!
- That's enough playtime.
- Hmm?
Jab! Jab! Jab! Jab! Jab!
Stay out of the way!
Final blow!
Idiot!
Keep your eyes on the fight.
Hyah!
What was all that? The kicks!
Oh, well, uh...
Wow! I think you hit
every one of his weak points.
It turns out he was pretty easy to beat.
Was he really though?
I'm fairly sure he got a blow in.
Hmph. That little baby hit wasn't nothing.
Are you sure you're okay?
I barely remember it, 'cause it
doesn't hurt--
Huh? Don't pretend it doesn't hurt
when it literally makes you cry.
I knew it. You seemed distracted
in the fight earlier.
Huh?
Wait. Wh... What the heck are these?
You should ask Kuno, not me.
He bought them off of me.
I wanted a little extra cash.
You what?
Ha! All these pictures are so
boring anyway, who would even want them?
If we compare the two of us, you don't
even have half the sex appeal that I do.
Hmm?
OSTEOPATHIC CLINIC -
CHIROPRACTOR
ACUPUNCTURE - ACUPRESSURE
Hmm. You're in bad shape.
Aside from this nasty bokuto strike,
you also have severe contusions
and dislocations.
Who was it that did this?
Well, uh...
It was...
Hmm?
A girl who suffers from
no sex appea--
Oh, I'm so sorry!
Was this your doing, Akane?
Uh, maybe, but it's because...
Pfft. Yeah, now you're doing
the cute girl act.
Mmm.
I knew it.
It was obvious it was you right away.
The way you dislocated
this joint in particular.
So interesting to see
your signature move this way.
Really?
So, you're Ranma, right?
I heard you were chosen
to be Akane's fiancé.
Our parents made that decision
on their own.
Yes, it's a bit early for all that.
The two of you are still kids.
I guess so.
So I'm still a kid.
Stop! That hurts.
Oh! Well that's strange.
Where are you still hurting?
What? Oh, uh...
Huh? Hey.
- Dr. Tofu is very good at his job.
- Hmm.
- Oh, Ranma, can we talk?
- Hmm?
Yeah?
Regardless of your betrothal,
do try and get along with Akane.
It's not like I go out of my way
to pick a fight with her.
She's the one who keeps picking on me.
But still. She's a real sweet girl.
Is she?
You'll understand one day.
What were you two talking about?
Ah, nothing.
Only that you're a lot to handle
'cause you're such a tomboy.
Huh. Coming at me?
- I see.
- Huh?
Hmm?
Hmm? Hmm?
I was just kidding.
Getting all girlie and heartbroken now.
What are you trying to say?
There you are.
I almost didn't recognize you
without you getting mad at me.
- What did you say?
- Whoa.
- Get back here.
- Too slow!
Four, three, two, one.
Whoa.
What's the matter with you?
My legs. Oh.
Ugh, that jerk. He must've done something
when he patted my back earlier.
All right. Guess I don't have a choice.
Uh, wait. What are you doing?
Piggyback. You can't walk, can you?
I... No way!
That's so embarrassing for a man to...
That's cold!
It shouldn't be a problem
if we're both girls.
I'm not too heavy, am I?
Stop worrying about it.
You can't even stand up.
- She's a real sweet girl.
- I guess she can be.
You'll understand one day.
Nope, still not getting it.
ANYTHING GOES MARTIAL ARTS
TENDO DOJO
Mr. Saotome, and Ranma too.
Your breakfast is ready now.
Oh.
- Thanks for telling us, Kasumi.
- No, no, no. Whoa!
STARTING TODAY, I HAVE
A PART-TIME JOB. - GENMA SAOTOME
You got a job? You planning on working
part-time in a zoo?
'Cause, uh...
WRONG!
Could you pass the soy sauce?
Morning training, huh? Well, good for you.
Good morning.
Dang, it's hot!
Come on now, Ranma.
Are you missing any sense of modesty?
Oh, to hell with all that. Screw modesty.
You have no shame.
Like a tomboy has any right
to try and shame me.
Before I forget,
could you two stop by Dr. Tofu's office
on your way back?
If it's okay, I'd like you
to return the book I borrowed.
You can't do it yourself?
I'm a little too busy today.
Oh, okay.
Yeah, I guess I can go do it.
But that would be the perfect excuse--
We'll be late.
No!
- A-Akane, wait just a second!
- Shut up!
Ranma, you need to keep
that big mouth shut!
Come on now. What's that supposed to mean?
I was clear.
Keep that big mouth of yours shut.
Uh...
This is why I was telling you to wait.
I didn't realize.
What the hell are you all doing?
Wanting a free show?
Who wants to go first?
Akane Tendo.
We will no longer challenge you to fight.
Wha...
We all agreed.
We decided to accept the fact
that you're engaged now.
Huh?
That's what this is about?
But why now?
Well, rumor has it
that Ranma Saotome defeated me.
Which is such an absurd falsehood.
However, I refuse to be defeated!
Kuno was the strongest person left
at Furinkan High School.
But he was also
the biggest pervert of us all.
What on earth did you just call me?
I won't give up.
I'll battle any coward like Ranma.
They can kick me a hundred times over.
I refuse to process the pain.
Who do you think you're calling
a coward?
Hmm?
You don't have to be
such a sore loser, you know.
Whoa!
My little lady with the braid is
finally here.
Seriously, you need to remember
what gender you are.
I've missed you so.
But wait a sec.
I thought Akane was the one you liked.
Of course I do.
She's watching, you know.
- Hmm?
- How did I not realize, Kuno?
If you like her more,
then I'll happily step aside.
Oh.
Akane Tendo!
What are you talking about?
Her offer to step aside is
so endearing.
And she's so adorable, I can't let go.
I love both of you!
Whoa!
That was great, Saotome.
Well, yeah. Didn't he study acrobatics
or something when he went to China?
It was kempo.
By the way, how far have you gotten
with Akane?
Hmm?
Come on, we know she's your fiancée.
Don't play dumb.
Huh?
So you guys must be doing
some pretty freaky stuff, am I right?
No. Nothing.
You liar. I'm betting
you two are crazy dirty.
How much insane sex do you do
every day, bro?
We don't do anything!
Get it, Akane!
Yeah!
Way to go!
All right. Now it's our turn.
- Damn. Look at how cute she is.
- Huh?
That girl is in no way cute.
Besides, she has a crush
on someone else anyway.
Yeah?
Hey, Saotome.
Aren't you supposed to be a kempo expert?
Mm-hmm.
I guess kempo doesn't do
too much blocking or dodging.
I was a little distracted.
I'm sorry. Does it still hurt?
Hey, I've apologized to you,
like, 30 times now.
Hmm?
Oh, hey.
Old Man?
What are you doing here in the street?
Really?
So my new hire is your father?
You two don't look much alike.
By the way, what happened to your face?
Accident in P.E. class.
I have an ointment that will work wonders
on that. Just one second.
Hmm?
AAARGH! PANDAS CAN'T TALK!
So why did you pick up the phone?
Hello? How can I help you today?
Uh...
Sure. Understood. 'Kay, bye.
I'm gonna head home.
Did something end up happening?
No, not really.
Great. Why you heading off in such a rush?
I mean, you like the doctor. Hmm?
Stop it.
There's already another person
that he likes, okay?
That was her on the phone.
She said she'll be coming over soon.
Hello? Good afternoon.
Whoa! She's the one he has a crush on?
He's got a type.
Not her!
You're leaving already, Kasumi?
Just heading to the chiropractor.
Kasumi?
Dr. Tofu has a crush on Kasumi.
It's obvious from the way he acts.
Hey, you two. What are you doing out here?
Uh, n-nothing at all.
R-Right?
So much for heading out.
Now, let's see the damage.
Oh. A mark from a ball.
Akane must have hit this one, right?
The depth and angle of the stitches were
what ultimately gave it away.
Wow. So you can tell
how feral she is just from that?
Come on! You weren't paying attention
so this is your fault.
- Oh.
- Ah.
Sorry. I was just joking around.
Uh...
Dummy.
There's nothing wrong with it.
You know? It's good to stay active.
- But, still...
- It's good that you're so healthy.
Not sexy though.
Good afternoon.
Oh, Kasumi.
Uh...
Hello?
Did I hear a wet snap just now?
Hey, Kasumi.
Oh. Hi, Ranma. What's wrong?
Nothing wrong.
He started coming in recently.
Right, Ranma?
I SAID I'M RANMA'S POP!
Hey, Doc?
So, how can I help you?
Oh, yes.
Bringing back the book I borrowed.
Hey, Doc?
Also, I wasn't sure if you wanted these.
Oh, thank you.
It's a mask, isn't it?
No, that wasn't the gift.
- Dr. Tofu.
- This is great.
- I'm stuck.
- Actually, that's the plate.
Doctor!
Hmm. Uh, something I can help you with?
My neck hurts!
Another injury? All right then.
Are you serious?
Sit, sit.
I can fix that right up actually.
Here.
I'm sorry, Mr. Saotome,
would you mind getting Kasumi some tea?
HEY! OVER HERE!
Dr. Tofu is always so funny to watch,
wouldn't you say?
Oh, you think?
He never acts like this
whenever you're not around, big sister.
Oh?
What's she doing? Is she crying?
I don't like feeling this way.
Oh!
Ow!
Well, I guess that proves you're fine.
Please don't tell me that was
your crappy attempt at cheering me up.
Oopsy-daisy.
What's that supposed to mean?
- Of course I was.
- Hmm?
Oh, my neck is fixed.
Okay. Wanna keep me company?
Hmm?
Come on. Take a swing!
I don't know...
Here I come!
Whoa!
I'm trying to blow off some steam here,
so stop playing and let's go!
Come on, now. Doesn't it get tiring
being this angry all the time?
You don't need to worry about that.
You know what I was thinking?
You're really cute when you smile.
Huh?
Gotcha.
No fair! That one doesn't count.
Let's go again!
You're really cute when you smile.
Did he mean that?
What's with this face you got going on?
That's a creepy smirk.
So, your neck still hasn't healed yet?
It was healed for, like, a minute.
CHIROPRACTIC